Munkhburen "Munduu" Munkhbileg

(405) 226-3998 • www.linkedin.com/in/munduu-munkhburen • mmunkhbileg9@ou.edu

PROFILE

Data Scientist with strong math background and 3+ years of experience in developing ML models to solve challenging business problems

Proficient in collaborating with teams of professionals for developing applications and solutions for business growth

EDUCATION

University of Oklahoma - Norman, OK Master's degree in Information Technology Bachelor's degree in Information System UWC Atlantic College - Llantwit major, Wales, UK

Expected December 2022 Expected December 2022

May 2018

International Baccalaureate Diploma

CERTIFICATIONS

Machine Learning Specialization, Algorithms, Stanford University, CourseraAugust 2022TensorFlow Developer, TensorFlow: Advanced Techniques, Deep Learning, DeepLearning.AlJuly 2022Machine Learning Engineer on Google Cloud, Google CloudJuly 2022Machine Learning Scientist, The DataCampDecember 2021Machine Learning Engineer, EducativeDecember 2021

SKILLS & TALENT

Tools & Languages: Python, C#, REST API, R, SQL, PowerBI, Tableau, Excel, Google Cloud Platform **Packages:** Pandas, Sklearn, Keras, TensorFlow, PyTorch, Spark, NumPy, Matplotlib, XGBoost, Django, SwiftUI **Statistics/Machine Learning:** Deep Neural Network, Graph Neural Network, CNN, NLP, Webservice, IOS **Relevant Coursework:** Machine Learning, Advanced Machine Learning, Applied Machine Learning, Data Science and Analytics, Business Data Analysis.

RELEVANT EXPERIENCE

Data Science Research Assistant, Price College of Business, Norman, OK

Feb 2022 - Current

- Extracting valuable insights from multiple sources of data (including Twitter and Instagram) with the help of Deep Learning and Artificial Intelligence.
- Development of methods to optimize and automate business processes.
- Applications of methods Recommender Systems for influencer-brand collaborations on Instagram;
 Understanding diffusion of information on Twitter using deep learning models; Using advanced Natural Language processing to understand brand activism on Twitter.

Machine Learning Research Intern, EMR Technical Solution, Edmond, OK

Jan 2022 – Feb 2022

- Investigated automating PostgreSQL using non derivative optimizations
- Tested model that configured over 300 knobs using Bayesian optimization

Data Scientist/ Machine Learning Engineer, Interactive, Ulaanbaatar, Mongolia Biggest business analytics and solution company in Mongolia

June 2020 – August 2021 www.interactive.mn

- Worked with other data scientists to develop analytics and other statistical analysis for partner companies
- Developed automated text reply for medical emergency application
- Tested machine learning models & improved results for more than 40 partnering companies
- Built car recognition system for partner gas station

Deep Learning Project

- Successfully implemented semantic labeling for satellite picture using Autoencoders with over 97% accuracy
- Implemented Attention mechanism to find biological family for sequence of amino acid
- Made custom inception deep network using TensorFlow functional API to classify real time image
- Built LSTM prediction model for Apple's stock with over 95% accuracy to enable informed investment

Data Science Project

- Designed ERD, implemented database system for tire company using Microsoft SQL Server
- Performed clusters to find unique group for each influencers using their Bio with word2vec and Sklearn

OTHER EXPERIENCE

Product Manager Intern, TASO Construction - Ulaanbaatar, Mongolia

May 2019 – September 2019

- Learned to work with others to conduct research as part of the planning process
- Researched new technology to improve product quality
- Conducted financial analysis on new upcoming products

Integrated Business Core Program, Price College of Business

August 2019 – December 2019

Sales Manager, Inventory Manager

- Manufactured sweater that designed by our group with unique logo
- Sold over \$5000 worth of sweater and served 800 hours for local community
- Best seller of the company